(Leonard:)Nice shot.
Thank you.
(Sheldon:)My father taught me archery
as a child.
(Sheldon:)It's odd how the activity
(Sheldon:)brings back the smell
of Kmart bourbon.
(Leonard:)Perfect.
I know.
(Sheldon:)What an elf
I would have made.
(Sheldon:)Whoo.
(Sheldon:)What do you think you're doing?
(Leonard:)Shooting at a target?
(Sheldon:)With what?
(Leonard:)An arrow.
Really?
(Sheldon:)I didn't see you draw one
from your quiver.
(Leonard:)I'm not going to do that,
Sheldon.
(Sheldon:)Leonard, the people at Nintendo
can only go so far
(Sheldon:)in helping us recreate
an actual athletic experience.
(Sheldon:)We have to do our part, too.
(Sheldon:)That was uncalled for,
but...